The name on the receipt is mine
I also wrote the notes
But whether that little boy
from 15 years ago is Fu Chenzhou
I can't just make him owe me a favor
Your past should be returned to you by evidence
Not claimed by me
Mrs. Fu, you are quite exceptional
Mr. Qin
I just feel that identity and favors
aren't things you can steal
Seeing you not fight for it
even when you have all the evidence
Just because I have the evidence
doesn't mean I should dictate the outcome
If you really were that person back then
I want you to know the truth
But I don't want you to feel
obligated to me because of the truth
We are already married
I want you to stay by my side
because you want to
not because you owe me
From now on, tell me first
I'll help you find the evidence
One ginkgo leaf pendant
One original hospital receipt
One piece of dark blue fabric
Please state how you obtained these
items along with the time and place
Mr. Qin, I was just too anxious
Being anxious doesn't change where they came from
Mr. Fu, I didn't mean to lie to you